

SHISHIR SINGH

BUSINESS DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Phone: +917089389916

Email: singhshishir523@gmail.com

Address: 11/9 sirmour road rewa

near KV.2 school

EDUCATION

2020 - 2023

Sk Somaiya College Mumbai

Bachelor of commerce (Honours)

Marketing and Sales

2 years-8 cgpa

2019-2020

Macro Vision Academy

Intermediate (XII) CBSE - 82.2 %

2017-2018

Macro Vision Academy

Higher Secondary (X) CBSE - 57%

SKILLS

- Marketing
- Interpersonal skill
- Communication
- Data analyst
- Canva
- Team Work

PERSONAL PROFILE

Shishir Singh is an experienced Sales Representative who has worked in different companies for 6 months. With impeccable skills and experience in selling products and meeting sales targets, Shishir will be a beneficial addition to a company's overall business operations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

18/05/2022 - 18/08/2022

Catking Educare

Campus Ambassador

- Answer 200+ customer questions regarding product, price and availability and done student counselling also.
- · Achieved target of every month.
- · Conducted seminar in school and college campus.

5/10/2022-10/01/2023

Bada Business pvt.Itd

Sales Executive

- Generated 50 new clients during tenure with an average of 3 months
- Average 16-25 outside cold call daily,25+ phone calls to produce 3-6
 per qualified appointment per week .
- · Improve profitability by growing customers base.